(Page:)Fidelity, bravery, integrity.
(Sheldon:)Correct. Now to business.
(Sheldon:)18 years ago, I sent
the FBI Crime Lab samples
(Sheldon:)from a bag of excrement
that had been lit on fire
(Sheldon:)on my front porch...
(Sheldon:)...for fingerprinting
and DNA analysis.
(Sheldon:)Why haven't I heard back yet?
(Page:)Well, the FBI Crime Lab
does have a lot on its plate.
(Sheldon:)That's of little comfort
to a nation
(Sheldon:)attempting to scrape
burning feces off its shoes.
(Page:)Would you mind if we talked
about Mr. Wolowitz now?
(Sheldon:)A little, but go on.
(Woman at Door:)Thank you.
(Page:)Would you characterize him
as responsible?
(Sheldon:)I'm going to answer that
with a visual aid.
(Sheldon:)This is my nine-disc complete
Lord of the Rings trilogy
Blu-ray set.
(Sheldon:)Mr. Wolowitz borrowed it,
(Sheldon:)damaged plastic retention
hub number three...